<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>887 blog</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on 887 blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 16:09:59 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Project progress</title><link>/posts/2023-10-07/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 16:09:59 +0200</pubDate><guid>/posts/2023-10-07/</guid><description>My rust project is on track Not much more to say there. Day by day i&amp;rsquo;m making progress.
The &amp;lsquo;Anyhow&amp;rsquo; crate is great.
Living and loving developing.
Blogging feels like procrastinating still, so i better get back to coding and physically working out.
This is nice, but actually doing &amp;lsquo;something&amp;rsquo; i can quantify,
like the compiler no longer yelling at me, there being a product or thing i can label &amp;lsquo;done&amp;rsquo; or my mind agreeing with that it&amp;rsquo;s progress makes me feel more productive.</description></item><item><title>Working on new idea</title><link>/posts/2023-05-02/</link><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2023 20:44:07 +0200</pubDate><guid>/posts/2023-05-02/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;ve got a challenging idea brewing Instead of blogging about it i should keep working on it. Before starting a quick post.
Most of coding isn&amp;rsquo;t just coding, but doing research, writing tools, etc. I usually try not to develop a solution if there is a usable solution i can adapt. This isn&amp;rsquo;t the case on this. I&amp;rsquo;ll have to do the heavy lifting.
I used flutter yesterday, which is really nice.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:47:55 +0200</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>Why 887? It&amp;rsquo;s a prime number and has 3 letters. That&amp;rsquo;s it. No deeper meaning behind it. I can type it on my keyboard hitting the keys really fast. That&amp;rsquo;s why.
Hi, i&amp;rsquo;m a software dev. Most of the software that i ended up writing over the decades has been for my employer or personal projects. So you can&amp;rsquo;t find my projects here on github. That&amp;rsquo;s &amp;lsquo;what happened&amp;rsquo;. I do use and support open source.</description></item><item><title>Red Rising</title><link>/books/red-rising/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:01:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>/books/red-rising/</guid><description>I read this and all following books in the series and highly recommend it. The philosophy in the original first three books inspired me deeply.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red_Rising</description></item><item><title>Welcome to my blog</title><link>/posts/2023-04-30/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 18:40:39 +0200</pubDate><guid>/posts/2023-04-30/</guid><description>Introduction So, i avoided blogging for ages and instead messaged people on various platforms or wrote to myself in files or a personal discord. So i&amp;rsquo;m starting a blog in 2023? Yes, mostly because it&amp;rsquo;s all markdown in the backend, and markdown is great to edit, for the most part 🙃. Since messaging people my thoughts is highly inefficient and wastes their time, more likely than not, i&amp;rsquo;m gonna write to my self on this nifty blog.</description></item></channel></rss>