<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Books on 887 blog</title><link>/books/</link><description>Recent content in Books on 887 blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 14:50:51 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The First Law</title><link>/books/the-first-law/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Dec 2023 14:50:51 +0100</pubDate><guid>/books/the-first-law/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s violent and dark. Very graphical. But it&amp;rsquo;s a very well done. The character development and philosophy made me continue on reading it. In the second book a lot of things come together and it&amp;rsquo;s great. I would say this is getting better with an exponential curve, about 60% through the second book it will grip you hard if it hasn&amp;rsquo;t before.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_First_Law</description></item><item><title>The Three-Body Problem</title><link>/books/three-body-problem/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Sep 2023 16:01:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>/books/three-body-problem/</guid><description>The Dark Forest and wall facers/breakers are great concepts.
Time spent reading this get&amp;rsquo;s well rewarded. It really broadens your horizons.
I think the second book was the best and the last book felt like it could have been part of another series like the wandering earth by the same author.
But it was hard to finish this and it&amp;rsquo;s great SciFi and raises really good questions.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Three-Body_Problem_(novel)</description></item><item><title>Expeditionary Force</title><link>/books/x-force/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 16:01:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>/books/x-force/</guid><description>Skippy and Joe. The series starts like a hard military novel, turns into very well done star trek and it&amp;rsquo;s own thing.
We gotta talk about the attempt at doing space opera in the middle of the series, but i&amp;rsquo;ll blame that on skippy.
I bit of the hard military fiction went into it&amp;rsquo;s own series starting with &amp;rsquo;trouble on paradise&amp;rsquo; while the strategies and scheming stayed with joe.
It has lots of little cultural references and quips but i enjoyed all the books.</description></item><item><title>Foundation</title><link>/books/foundation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 23:01:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>/books/foundation/</guid><description>Asimov&amp;rsquo;s laws of robotics in i robot, bicentennial man and now foundation.
I watched all of this as movies growing up and now the TV show but only later in live i looked up who it all came from. Psycho-history indeed.
Egos, Games, People. Philosophy and ScFi.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Foundation_series</description></item><item><title>Infinite</title><link>/books/infinite/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 23:01:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>/books/infinite/</guid><description>I enjoyed infinite and infinite 2.
A lot of Jeremy Robinsons other recent novels will join in the series as a crossover now for Infinite 3. (Already happened with Torment in Infinite 2.)
I would say read the first two and only read the rest if you are looking for fun but not hard self-reflecting question.
They are all good in their own way, but if you read anything by Jeremy, read Infintie 1 and 2.</description></item><item><title>Red Rising</title><link>/books/red-rising/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 23:01:16 +0200</pubDate><guid>/books/red-rising/</guid><description>I read this and all following books in the series and highly recommend it. The philosophy in the original first three books inspired me deeply.
https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Red_Rising</description></item></channel></rss>